surveyteam.com 2008-12-18

# ::Welcome to Survey Team::

**PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT**

**Revised 15th June 2006**  
Your privacy is very important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how surveyteam.com collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our Web site.  
surveyteam.com has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of users like you because your privacy is of utmost importance to us. 

**I. INFORMATION COLLECTION**

1\. **Information Collected**

All Users must provide the following information in order to join surveyteam: name, mailing address, phone number, email address, username, and password. Users may be required to provide subsequent demographic information in order to receive Signup Bonus(es) and/or qualify for other promotions. Demographic information includes, but is not limited to: birth date, gender, marital status, education completed, and household income. 

2\. **Means of Collection**

Currently, the only way to join surveyteam is through one of our signup forms. We do not acquire Users through purchase, co-registration, or any other means; however, we may do so at any time in the future. 

**II. USE OF INFORMATION**

1\. **Use of Information**

User information is used by surveyteam in all of the following, but not limited to, ways: 

**(a)** E-Mail Address is used to send paid email advertisements and important announcements about SureyTeam to User   
**(b)** User will have to provide US verified primary PayPal Account to receive payments.   
**(c)** Demographic information is used to target advertisements to User.   
**(d)** Username and Password are used for user protection to restrict access to their account. 

2\. **Sharing of Information**

surveyteam does not rent, sell, or share User information, except in the following circumstances: 

**(a)** We are required to release User information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes.   
**(b)** We are sold to or acquired by another company, in which case all User information would then belong to the said company.   
**(c)** We share User information when co-registration boxes (explained below) are checked during the course of registration.   
**(d)** We suspect a User of committing fraud, in which case User information may be shared during the course of our investigation.   
**(e)** We provide User information to trusted partners in order to enhance the service provided to our Users. 

**III. CO-REGISTRATION**

1\. **Definition**

Surveyteam signup pages may contain co-registration checkboxes, where Users can choose to "co-register" for other Web Sites during their registration with surveyteam by checking the checkbox next to the co-registration Offer. Users are not required to select any co-registration boxes to join surveyteam; however, they may be required to do so in order to qualify for Signup Bonus(es) and/or other promotions. 

2\. **Information Sharing**

When a User co-registers for an Offer by checking the co-registration checkbox, any information they provide to SurveyTeam may be shared with the Advertiser associated with the co-registration Offer. SurveyTeam cannot control what Advertisers subsequently do with that information. 

**IV. COOKIES**

1\. **Referral and Affiliate Tracking**

SurveyTeam uses cookies in order to track new User registrations. This ensures Users are properly credited for referring other Users, as well as to track earnings for our Affiliates. 

2\. **User Recognition**

After a User has logged into the SurveyTeam Member's Section, cookies are used to remember their Username and Password so they do not need to be entered during every visit to our Web Site. Users can logout of the Member's Section if they do not wish to have this information saved. 

3\. **Cookies are Safe!**

Cookies used by SurveyTeam can only be seen by SurveyTeam, and cannot in any way cause harm to your computer. Because we cannot properly track user actions without the use of Cookies (to ensure Users are credited for completing Offers, referring friends, etc), our Web Site will not function properly for Users who have Cookies disabled. 

4. **AGE REQUIRMENT**

The 'surveyteam.com' service is unavailable to persons under the age of 13. 

**DATA SECURITY**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, surveyteam.com has used appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. However, no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, surveyteam.com cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us or from our sponsors and you do so at your own risk. 

**V. CALIFORNIA USER CONSUMER RIGHTS**

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov 

**EXTERNAL LINKS**

surveyteam.com is not responsible for any content or privacy policies of web sites not operated by surveyteam.com. 

**OPTING-OUT**

surveyteam.com members are opted-in to receive surveyteam.com newsletters at the time of enrollment. You may opt-out of by following the directions enclosed in the newsletter. 

**CANCELING**

You may cancel your Membership at anytime by  unsubscribing here . If you decide to cancel your membership and later wish to re-enroll, you will be assigned a new account ID and you will not receive credit for earnings made using your previous account. Surveyteam.com reserves the right to terminate or suspend any account at any time with or without notice. surveyteam.com does not tolerate any abuse, harassment, or fraudulent activity aimed towards other members or surveyteam.com. Changes To The Privacy Policy: By registering to use the surveyteam.com service, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that surveyteam.com privacy policy may change from time to time. We strongly advise our members to check back from time to time. We also welcome any feedback from you; please email us at [support@surveyteam.com](mailto:support@surveyteam.com)if you have any comments regarding the information or improvements that can be made to this privacy policy. 

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [support@surveyteam.com](mailto:support@surveyteam.com)

Innovative Ideas, Inc.   
1540 E Dundee Road, Ste 108   
Palatine, IL 60074-2362
